Quirini, Helen; Papers apap102
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Community Activism, 1898-2010; Undated; 6
  - Senior Citizens, 1972-2010; Undated; 6.5; 4.53 cubic ft.
    Quirini also joined the Public Service Commissions Albany Area Senior Citizen Advisory Council in the mid-1980s. This group advised on customer expectations and utility needs from a seniors perspective. One of key recurring issues was the increasing costs of telephone service. In 1992 this Advisory Council joined with other special needs consumer groups to form the Public Service Commissions Capital District Utility Consumer Advisory Council. Quirini remained on this newly formed Council until at least 1993. Agendas, meeting minutes, notes, correspondence and reports from Quirinis tenure on both Councils are present.
    In addition to her work with area organizations, Quirini also became involved in national issues most relevant to seniors. Qurini fought for the repeal of the Medicare Catastrophic Coverage Act of 1988 which she argued had modest benefits and would burden elder Medicare recipients with extra costs and taxes. Qurini chaired mass informational meetings of area seniors groups to discuss the Medicare Catastrophic Coverage Act in 1988 and 1989. These featured state and local legislators, individual seniors and leaders of senior citizen groups as speakers. Notes, speeches, photographs and flyers from these events and general background materials about the legislation are in this series.
    The IUE nominated Quirini to attend the New York State Governors Conference on Aging in March 1995. She subsequently served as part of the New York delegation to the White House Conference on Aging held in May 1995. This series features materials from both conferences, including official reports and resolutions as well as Quirinis correspondence and notes.
    Other items of interest in this series are pamphlets written by Quirini on a variety of issues affecting seniors and materials about the Social Security Notch provision which affected benefits paid to individuals, like Quirini, born between 1917 and 1921.
    Please see Series 5 for materials related to Quirini's work with the GE Retirees on behalf of pension reform.
    - AARP Certificate of Appreciation for Helen Quirini, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Events and Programs, 1986; 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Meeting Minutes, Treasurer's Reports and Financials, 1987-1990 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Meeting Minutes, Treasurer's Reports and Financials, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, The Reporter Newsletter, 1987; 1989-1998 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Photographs at Universal Health Care Rally, 1992 April 15 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Resolutions, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - AARP Chapter #490, Schenectady County, Standing Rules and Committee Overview, 1987; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - AARP Chapter Activity Reports, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - AARP Chapter Officers, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - AARP Correspondence, 1983; 1987-1990; 1992; 2003; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - AARP Literature, 1985; 1987; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - AARP and New York State Senior Action Council Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1989-199; Undated (Flat-file 2)
    - AARP Women's Initiative and Women's History, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO Committee to Study Nursing Homes, Reports, Correspondence and Notes, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO Committee to Study Nursing Homes, Reports, Correspondence and Notes, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO Retirees Council, "America's Nursing Homes: Profit in Human Misery,", 1977 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - The Annie Schaffer Senior Services Center, Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Brookdale Center on Aging, 1993; 1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Capital District Consortium on Aging, Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Capital District Senior Issues Forum, Lifetime Achievement Award, 2005 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, AARP Coverage, News Clippings, and Correspondence, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Abstracts, Excerpts from Articles, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Advocates Senior Alert Process, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, The Annie Schaefer Senior Center, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, "CATCAP Isn't What It Appears", 1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Clippings from Solidarity Notes, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Clippings of Letters to the Editor, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Congressional Record, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Congressional Research Service Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Correspondence with U.S. and New York Executives, Senators and Members of the House, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Fact Sheets, Leaflets and Handbills, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, "Golden Pamphlet" by Helen Quirini, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Handwritten Notes, 1987; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, IRS Reports, AARP Reports, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Legislation, Resolutions and Abstracts, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Legislation Text of Medicare Catastrophic Coverage Act, 1988 July 01 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Memorandums, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Welfare, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, New York Assembly Legislature Resolution, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, New York Assembly Legislature Resolution, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, New York Senate Legislature Resolution, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, News Clippings and Articles, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43-44)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Rally Against the Act, 1989 May 18 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Rally Against the Act Photographs, 1989 May 19 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2-3)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Seniors Action Coalition/Seniors Against Catastrophic Act, 1988-1994; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4-5)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, Signed Petitions, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, The Villers Advocacy Associates Correspondence, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - Catastrophic Coverage Act, "What You Need to Know About the New Medicare Catastrophic Coverage Act," by Prentice Hall Editorial Staff, 1988 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, New York State Nursing Home Patient Ombudsman Program, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from Helen Quirini with State and National Legislators, 1989; 1994-1996 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Assemblyman Paul Tonko Regarding Seniors, Utilities, 1990 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - Day Haven Adult Day Care, Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - Empire Blue Cross and Blue Shield, Medigap Insurance - [RESTRICTED], 1992-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - Expanded In-Home Service for the Elderly Program, 1988; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - Gray Panthers, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Kryzak, Rose, Eulogy and Legacy Fund, Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Legislative Status of 1983 Bills Affecting the Elderly, Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Long-Term Care, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Mohawk Valley Senior research Center Senior Community Forum on Aging Issues, 2000 August 29 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - New York Senior COPES Plan, Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - New York Assembly Hearing on Pending Medicare Changes Testimony Including Comments from Helen Quirini, 1995 October 24 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - New York State Celebrates Senior Citizens' Day, Pamphlet Recognizing Helen Quirini and Others, 2005 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - New York State Conference for the Aging Legislative Conference, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - New York State Elderly and Energy Conference Materials, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Agendas, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Background Materials, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Conference Binder, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27-28)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Follow-up Materials Including Recommendations, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Pre-Conference Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - New York State Governor's Conference on Aging, Resolutions, Recommendations and Notes Taken by Helen Quirini, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - New York State Public Service Commission's Community Outreach Day, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - New York State Senate Democratic Task Force on Health Care, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council 25th Anniversary Dinner Celebration, 1997 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council 30th Anniversary Celebration, 2002 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Advocacy Packet, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Annual Convention Binder, 2001 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Annual Convention Materials, 1972; 1987; 1989-1990; 1992-1997 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Annual Convention Materials, 1999-2003 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Annual Convention Materials, 2004-2008 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Award Materials, 2003 (Box 2 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Board Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Board Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Board Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council By-Laws, 1987-1988; 1991; 1998; 2003; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Capital Region Chapter Materials, 2004; 2006-2007 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Correspondence, 1987; 2006-2007 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Events, 2001; 2006; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Grassroots Senior Citizens Day, 2000-2003; 2005 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council History and Background Information, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Legislative Activities, 1996; 1999-2003 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Letters to the Editor Sent by Helen Quirini, 2002; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Literature, Ads and Mailings, 1990; 1999; 2004; 2006; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council News Releases, 1988; 1996-1997; 2002 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Personal Records and Planning Book Prepared by Helen Quirini, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Region 5 Materials, 1990; 1992; 1996-1997; 1999-2003; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Reorganization, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Resolutions, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Social Insurance Organizing Project, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council StateWide Sentinel, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Testimony About Medicaid/Health, 1997 January 30 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council Testimony on the Executive Budget Including Comments from Helen Quirini, 2003 February 10 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action Council "Vote to Protect Social Security and Medicare" Bumper Sticker, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - New York StateWide Senior Action News, 1988 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - New York Universal Health Care Rally at the Annie Shaffer Senior Center Photographs, 1992 April 15 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - News Clippings About Assorted Senior Topics and Helen Quirini, 1980; 1984; 1987-1990; 2002; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - Niagara Mohawk and the Public Service Commission Materials Related to NiMo Service, 1997; 1999 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - Niagara Mohawk Free Pilot Lighting Service, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - Notes by Helen Quirini on Issues Affecting Seniors, 1995; 1999; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - Nursing Home Community Coalition of New York State, Statewide Annual Convention, 1999 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - Opposition to Medicare Cuts Petition, 1995; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Pamphlets Created by Helen Quirini About Health Care, Prescriptions and Medicare, 1987; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Physicians Participating in Medicare, 1984; 1992 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - Public Citizen Prescription Drug Fairness Material, 1999 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - Raycroft, Catherine, 1974-2009; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - Riitano, Deborah, 1996-2007; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Award of Merit from YWCA, 1987 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations By-Laws, 2006; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Correspondence (Incoming) - [RESTRICTED], 1985-2010; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Correspondence (Outgoing), 1985-2007; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Events, 1987; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Financial and Administrative Materials, 1999-2006; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1982-1983; 1985-1993; 1995-2002; 2006-2007; Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43-44)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Personal Records and Planning Book, Undated (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 45)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Treasurer's Reports, 1992-2002 (Box 3 (6-Community Activism), Folder 46)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Petitions, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Petitions About Gross Receipts Tax, 1992 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 2)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Petitions About Niagara Mohawk Rate Increases, 1994 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 3)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Senior Volunteer Recognition Day, 1986; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 4)
    - Schenectady County Council of Senior Citizen Organizations Trust Fund Statements - [RESTRICTED], 1986-1991; 1994 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 5)
    - Schenectady County Newsletter of Seniors Events Written by Helen Quirini, 2001 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 6)
    - Schenectady County Office for the Aging Senior Citizen of the Year Award Materials, 1990; 2005 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 7)
    - Schenectady Explores Senior Creativity Conference Materials, 1984 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 8)
    - Senior Action, 1993-1999 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 9)
    - Senior Action, 2000-2002 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 10)
    - Senior Action, 2003; 2005-2006 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 11)
    - Senior Action On-Line News from Albany Corresponding Newsletters, 1998-2000 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 12)
    - Senior Citizen Award for Isabel Shapnek, 1992 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 13)
    - Senior Issues Legislative Visit, 1988 February 10 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 14)
    - Social Security "Notch," AARP Materials, 1987; 1992; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 15)
    - Social Security "Notch," Correspondence, 1983-1988; 1990-1991; 1994; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 16)
    - Social Security "Notch," Fact Sheets, Handbills and Charts, 1987; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 17)
    - Social Security "Notch," National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Welfare Talking Points, 1991 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 18)
    - Social Security "Notch," New York Assembly Legislative Resolution, 1991 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 19)
    - Social Security "Notch," New York State Legislation, 1990 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 20)
    - Social Security "Notch," News Clippings, 1981-1994; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 21)
    - Social Security "Notch," Petitions, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 22)
    - Source Book and Regional Directory for Seniors, 1992 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 23)
    - Speech on Senior Issues by Helen Quirini, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 24)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission Albany Area Senior Citizen Advisory Council Meeting Minutes, Agendas and Correspondence, 1986; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 25)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission Capital District Utility Consumer Advisory Council Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 26)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission New York Telephone Rates, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 27)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission News Releases, Alerts and Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 28)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission Report Endorsing Model Utility Senior Program, 1988; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 29)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission Senior Advisory Councils Combined Meeting, 1987 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 30)
    - State of New York Public Service Commission Statement of Policy Endorsing Model Utility Senior Program, 1988 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 31)
    - Testimony at Office of Aging Hearing from Helen Quirini, 1986 May 22 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 32)
    - Untitled Photographs of Events for Seniors, 1986; 1989; Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 33)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Housing Resolution, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 34)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Adopted Resolutions, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 35)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Amendments to Resolutions from Interest Groups, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 36)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Background Materials, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 37)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Capital District Senior Groups Meeting, 1994 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 38)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Certificate of Recognition, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 39)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Citizen's Commission on Pension Policy, Undated (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 40)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Draft Resolutions, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 41)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Final Report Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 42)
    - White House Conference on Aging Final Report The Road to an Aging Policy for the 21st Century, 1996 (Oversized 18, Folder 2)
    - White House Conference on Aging Additional Final Resolutions, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Community Activism), Folder 43)
    - White House Conference on Aging, Helen Quirini Notes, Undated (Box 5 (6-Community Activism), Folder 1)